[	
	{
		"name":"People",
		"icon":"üö∂",
		"difficulty":"Easy",
		"content":[
			{"question":"M√§dchen", "answer":"Girl"},
			{"question":"Frau", "answer":"Woman"},
			{"question":"Herr", "answer":"Man"},
			{"question":"Mutter", "answer":"Mother"},
			{"question":"Vatter", "answer":"Father"},
			{"question":"Oma", "answer":"Grandmother"},
			{"question":"Gro√üvater", "answer":"Grandfather"},
			{"question":"Tante", "answer":"Aunt"},
			{"question":"Onkel", "answer":"Uncle"},
			{"question":"Bruder", "answer":"Brother"},
			{"question":"Schwester", "answer":"Sister"},
			{"question":"Freund", "answer":"Friend (Male)"},
			{"question":"Freundin", "answer":"Friend (Female)"},
		]
	},
	{
		"name":"Food/Drink",
		"icon": "üçî",
		"difficulty":"Easy",
		"content":[
			{"question":"Brot", "answer":"Bread"},
			{"question":"Wasser", "answer":"Water"},
			{"question":"Paprika", "answer":"Pepper"},
			{"question":"Zwiebel", "answer":"Onion"},
			{"question":"Saft", "answer":"Juice"},
			{"question":"K√§se", "answer":"Cheese"},
			{"question":"Huhn", "answer":"Chicken"},
			{"question":"Rind", "answer":"Beef"},
			{"question":"Gr√ºnkohl", "answer":"Kale"},
			{"question":"Bohnen", "answer":"Beans"},
			{"question":"Spinat", "answer":"Spinach"},
			{"question":"Pommes", "answer":"Fries"},
			{"question":"Salat", "answer":"Lettuce"},
			{"question":"Salz", "answer":"Salt"},
		]
	},
	{
		"name":"Clothes",
		"icon":"üëö",
		"difficulty":"Med",
		"content":[
			{"question":"Geldb√∂rse", "answer":"Purse"},
			{"question":"Hat", "answer":"Hat"},
			{"question":"Kapuzenpullover", "answer":"Hoodie"},
			{"question":"B√ºstenhalter", "answer":"Bra"},
			{"question":"Socken", "answer":"Socks"},
			{"question":"Handschuhe", "answer":"Gloves"},
			{"question":"Hose", "answer":"Pants"},
			{"question":"Damenslip", "answer":"Panties"},
			{"question":"Bluse", "answer":"Blouse"},
			{"question":"Weste", "answer":"Vest"},
			{"question":"Stiefel", "answer":"Boots"},
			{"question":"Strumpf", "answer":"Stockings"},
			{"question":"Strumpfg√ºrtel", "answer":"Garter Belt"},
			{"question":"Hausschuhe", "answer":"Slippers"},
			{"question":"Schmuck", "answer":"Jewelry"},
			{"question":"Pyjama", "answer":"Pajamas"},
			{"question":"G√ºrtel", "answer":"Belt"},
			{"question":"Schuhe", "answer":"Shoes"},
			{"question":"Damenmuskelshirt", "answer":"Tank Top"},
			{"question":"kurze Shorts", "answer":"Short Shorts"},
			
		]
	},
	{
		"name":"Verbs 1",
		"icon":"‚Ö§¬π",
		"difficulty":"Med",
		"content":[
			{"question":"Lernen", "answer":"To Learn"},
			{"question":"Laufen", "answer":"To Run"},
			{"question":"Springen", "answer":"To Jump"},
			{"question":"Sprechen", "answer":"To Speak"},
			{"question":"Singen", "answer":"To Sing"},
			{"question":"Fassen", "answer":"To Grab"},
			{"question":"Haben", "answer":"To Have"},
			{"question":"K√ºssen", "answer":"To Kiss"},
			{"question":"Gehen", "answer":"To Go"},
			{"question":"Kaufen", "answer":"To Buy"},
			{"question":"√úben", "answer":"To Exercise"},
			{"question":"Reiten", "answer":"To Ride"},
			{"question":"Lesen", "answer":"To Read"},
			{"question":"Kriechen", "answer":"To Crawl"},
			{"question":"Trinken", "answer":"To Drink"},
			{"question":"Sein", "answer":"To Be"},
			{"question":"Drehen", "answer":"To Turn"},
			{"question":"Heben", "answer":"To Lift"},
			{"question":"Dr√ºcken", "answer":"To Push"},
			{"question":"Ziehen", "answer":"To Pull"},
			{"question":"√ñffnen", "answer":"To Open"},
			{"question":"Schlie√üen", "answer":"To Close"},
			{"question":"Jagen", "answer":"To Chase"},
			{"question":"Essen", "answer":"To Eat"},
		]
	},
	{
		"name":"Misc 1",
		"icon":"‚ÖØ¬π",
		"difficulty":"Med",
		"content":[
			{"question":"Zeit", "answer":"Time"},
			{"question":"Jetzt", "answer":"Now"},
			{"question":"Jeden Falls", "answer":"Anyways"},
			{"question":"Geld", "answer":"Money"},
			{"question":"Bar", "answer":"Cash"},
			{"question":"B√§r", "answer":"Bear"},
			{"question":"Ausl√§nderin", "answer":"Foreigner (F)"},
			{"question":"Regierung", "answer":"Government"},
			{"question":"Landlich", "answer":"Rural"},
			{"question":"Auto", "answer":"Car"},
			{"question":"Bahn", "answer":"Train"},
			{"question":"Schlampe", "answer":"Slut XD"},
			{"question":"Liebe", "answer":"Love"},
			{"question":"Hass", "answer":"Hate"},
			{"question":"Gerechtigkeit", "answer":"Justice"},
		]
	},
	{
		"name":"Anatomy",
		"icon":"‚úã",
		"difficulty":"Hard",
		"content":[
			{"question":"Kopf", "answer":"Head"},
			{"question":"K√∂rper", "answer":"Body"},
			{"question":"Rumpf", "answer":"Torso"},
			{"question":"Arm", "answer":"Arm"},
			{"question":"Bein", "answer":"Leg"},
			{"question":"Gesicht", "answer":"Face"},
			{"question":"Mund", "answer":"Mouth"},
			{"question":"Zahn", "answer":"Tooth"},
			{"question":"Zunge", "answer":"Tongue"},
			{"question":"Auge", "answer":"Eye"},
			{"question":"Nase", "answer":"Nose"},
			{"question":"Ohr", "answer":"Ear"},
			{"question":"Haar", "answer":"Hair"},
			{"question":"Hals", "answer":"Neck"},
			{"question":"Bauch", "answer":"Tummy"},
			{"question":"Glied", "answer":"Penis"},
			{"question":"Scheide", "answer":"Vagina"},
			{"question":"Hoden", "answer":"Testicle"},
			{"question":"After", "answer":"Anus"},
			{"question":"H√ºfte", "answer":"Hip"},
			{"question":"Ellenbogen", "answer":"Elbow"},
			{"question":"Hand", "answer":"Hand"},
			{"question":"Finer", "answer":"Finger"},
			{"question":"Nagel", "answer":"Nail"},
			{"question":"Knei", "answer":"Knee"},
			{"question":"Fu√ü", "answer":"Foot"},
			{"question":"Zeh", "answer":"Toe"},
			{"question":"Gerhirn", "answer":"Brain"},
			{"question":"Herz", "answer":"Heart"},
			{"question":"Magen", "answer":"Stomach"},
			{"question":"Skelett", "answer":"Skeleton"},
		]
	},
	{
		"name":"Animals",
		"icon":"üêï",
		"difficulty":"Hard",
		"content":[
			{"question":"Hund", "answer":"Dog"},
			{"question":"Katze", "answer":"Cat"},
			{"question":"Ratte", "answer":"Rat"},
			{"question":"Kuh", "answer":"Cow"},
			{"question":"Pferd", "answer":"Horse"},
			{"question":"Esel", "answer":"Donkey"},
			{"question":"Schwein", "answer":"Pig"},
			{"question":"Schaf", "answer":"Sheep"},
			{"question":"Henne", "answer":"Chicken"},
			{"question":"Ziege", "answer":"Goat"},
			{"question":"Ente", "answer":"Duck"},
			{"question":"Gans", "answer":"Goose"},
			{"question":"Affe", "answer":"Monkey"},
			{"question":"B√§r", "answer":"Bear"},
			{"question":"Eichh√∂rnchen", "answer":"Squirrel"},
			{"question":"Elefant", "answer":"Elephant"},
			{"question":"Fledermaus", "answer":"Bat"},
			{"question":"Frettchen", "answer":"Ferret"},
			{"question":"Fuchs", "answer":"Fox"},
			{"question":"Hirsch", "answer":"Deer"},
			{"question":"Kaninchen", "answer":"Rabbit"},
			{"question":"Maus", "answer":"Mouse"},
			{"question":"L√∂we", "answer":"Lion"},
			{"question":"Tiger", "answer":"Tiger"},
			{"question":"Wolf", "answer":"Wolf"},
			{"question":"Delphin", "answer":"Dolphin"},
			{"question":"Seehund", "answer":"Deal"},
			{"question":"Wal", "answer":"Whale"},
			{"question":"Adler", "answer":"Eagle"},
			{"question":"Eule", "answer":"Owl"},
			{"question":"Falke", "answer":"Falcon"},
			{"question":"Pinguin", "answer":"Penguin"},
			{"question":"Truthahn", "answer":"Turkey"},
			{"question":"Seem√∂we", "answer":"Seagull"},
			{"question":"Hai", "answer":"Shark"},
			{"question":"Eidechse", "answer":"Lizard"},
			{"question":"Schlange", "answer":"Snake"},
			{"question":"Schildkr√∂te", "answer":"Turtle"},
			{"question":"Frosch", "answer":"Frog"},
			{"question":"Biene", "answer":"Bee"},
			{"question":"Fliege", "answer":"Fly"},
			{"question":"Ameise", "answer":"Ant"},
			{"question":"Gl√ºhwurm", "answer":"Firefly"},
			{"question":"Heuschrecke", "answer":"Grasshopper"},
			{"question":"Kafer", "answer":"Beetle"},
			{"question":"Marienk√§fer", "answer":"Ladybug"},
			{"question":"Motte", "answer":"Moth"},
			{"question":"Schabe", "answer":"Cockroach"},
			{"question":"Wespe", "answer":"Wasp"},
			{"question":"Spinne", "answer":"Spider"},
			{"question":"Krebs", "answer":"Crab"}
		]
	}
]